[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 17,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00_B",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 17,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Grace_00",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 17,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 19,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 20,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 20,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 20,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 21,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "Azoth_Vessel",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 21,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 21,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 23,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 24,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 24,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Captain",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21_B",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21_B_Unlock",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_objective_desc",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99A_Faction_Vector",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 17,
  "Task": "99A_Faction_Vector_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99A_Faction_Vector",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_Faction_Vector_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "99A_Faction_Vector_objective_title",
  "Description": "99A_Faction_Vector_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99A_Faction_Vector_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99A_Faction_Vector_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99A_Faction_Vector_incomplete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 }
]